arkaybeverages.com 2019-12-09

# Privacy Policy - ArKay Beverages - United States

We endeavor to protect your personal privacy. We provide this Privacy Policy to help you to understand what we may do with any personal information that we obtain from you. By providing your personal information to us, you signify your acceptance of our Privacy Policy and agree that we may collect, use and disclose your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy (“Policy”). All references to ‘our’, ‘us’, ‘we’ or ‘company’ within this Policy are deemed to refer to ArKayBeverages.com and its subsidiaries, affiliates and associates (collectively, “Arkay”).

The Policy is incorporated into and forms part of the Terms and Conditions of Use (“Terms”) which govern this site.

### Personal Information

It is understood that clear consent is given by you such that personal information given by you can be collected and processed by us in accordance with this Policy. Please read this Policy carefully to understand how we may collect, use and share your personal information and data related to you.

### Information We May Collect From You

In order to better provide you with numerous products and services, ArKaybeverages.com collects the following information about you:

  * Information that you provide by setting up an account on our website at [www.ArkayBeverages.com](http://www.arkaybeverages.com/) (“Website”).This includes personal information provided at the time of registering to use the service, posting material or requesting further services. We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with the Website;
  * If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence;
  * We may also ask you to complete surveys that are used for research purposes, although you do not have to respond to them;
  * Details of your visits to the Website including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data and the resources that you access; and
  * We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type. This is statistical data about your browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify you as an individual.

### Cookies

We use cookies and may allow others to use cookies in the operation of the Website. This is to obtain information about your general internet usage by using a cookie file which is stored on the hard drive of your computer and acceptance of the Terms constitutes provision by you of your express consent for us to use cookies.

You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting of cookies. If you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of the Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you log on to the Website.

### Who Is Collecting Your Information?

**Ad Servers and Content Servers**  
We may use third party ad servers or content servers to serve ads, product information, or other information both on and off our Website. Those third parties may use “action tags” or web beacons throughout the Website to count the number of visitors who click on a banner ad or other information and to track the number of customers who continue on to make a purchase. They may also place their own “cookie” on your computer to help those ads to run, analyze site usage and to provide you with personalized on-line advertisements.

**Image Servers**  
We use a third party image serving company to serve the graphics that visitors see on our Website more quickly. They collect a visitor’s IP address and the URLs of any graphics viewed and the date and time of the visit. They may also use their own “cookie.”

**Email Services**  
We use a third party to send promotional e-mails to customers. Images contained in the email may be served by the third party. They may use a “cookie” or “action tags.”

**Website Analysis Agent**  
We may contract with several online partners to help manage and optimize our Internet business and marketing. We use the services of marketing companies to help us measure the effectiveness of our advertising and how visitors use our Website. To do this, we use action tags and cookies provided by the marketing companies on this site. Although the marketing companies log the information coming from our Website on our behalf, we control how that data may and may not be used.

By using this website you agree and consent that your purchase order and choice of products, your  gender, your name , your address, your e-mail address and phone number may be used for analytics and that the information collected by Arkay Beverages shall be shared with Google Inc.

**Marketing Partners, Co-Branded Services, Framing/Windows on Third-Party Sites**  
We may run promotions for merchants where you may visit the merchants’ sites. In some of those promotions, a window or frame containing the merchant’s site may appear. Any time you are in a window, you should assume that your personal information is being collected, used and disclosed in accordance with that merchant’s policies. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information that you supply to those merchants. Any information that you share with them will be used and disclosed in accordance with that merchant’s privacy policy.

**Links and Banner Ads to Third-Party Sites**  
Please be aware that our Website may contain links to other sites on the Internet that are owned and operated by third parties. The information practices of those websites linking from or to our site are not covered by this Policy. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information for which we have no liability of responsibility.

### Disclosure Of Your Information

We may use, share and/or disclose personal information in one or more of the following ways:

**Marketing Communication and Advertising**  
To allow us to talk to you about our products and offer products and services to you. You may unsubscribe from such communication at any time.

Additionally, we may use cookies and other information to provide relevant interest-based advertising to you. Interest-based ads are ads presented to you based on your browsing behavior in order to provide you with ads more tailored to your interests. These interest-based ads may be presented to you while you are browsing our site or third-party sites not owned by Arkay. In the future, we may belong to ad networks that may use your browsing history across participating websites to show you interest-based advertisements on those websites. If and when we join an ad network, we will provide information on how to opt-out of this advertising. Other websites may also offer their own opt-out methods.

**Transactional Purposes**  
To enable us to provide online shopping, services and delivery for your convenience.

**Legal Purposes**  
In circumstances where;

  * Information that you provide by setting up an account on our website at [www.ArkayBeverages.com](http://www.arkaybeverages.com/) (“Website”).This includes personal information provided at the time of registering to use the service, posting material or requesting further services. We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with the Website;
  * We sell products, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller of such products;
  * If some or substantially all of our assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets;

We are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply the Terms; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of our company or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

Transfer in the Event if Sale of Change of Control. If the ownership of all or substantially all of our business (or the business of any of our subsidiaries or affiliates) changes or we otherwise transfer assets relating to our business (or the business of any of our subsidiaries or affiliates) or the Website to a third party, we may transfer your personal information to the new owner to be used consistent with this Privacy Policy. In such a case, your information would remain subject to the promises made in the applicable privacy policy.

### Third Party Sites

You should carefully review privacy policies of any third party sites accessible from the Website.

Other sites accessible through our Website have their own privacy policies and data collection, use and disclosure practices. Please consult each site’s privacy policy.

ArKaybeverages.com is not responsible for the policies or practices of third parties. Please be aware that this Website may contain links to other sites on the Internet that are owned and operated by third parties. The information practices of those web sites linked to Arkay are not covered by this Policy. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. Additionally, other companies that place advertising on our Website may collect information about you when you view or click on their advertising through the use of cookies. We cannot control this collection of information. You should contact these advertisers directly if you have any questions about their use of the information that they collect.

On behalf of various sponsors, ArKaybeverages.com provides sponsored links to third party web sites. If you click on a sponsored link or banner ad, a “window” or “frame” containing a third party’s web site may appear in the foreground with the Website in the background. Unless you are on the Website, any time that you have moved to a window, you should assume that your personal information is being collected, used and disclosed in accordance with the windowed site’s privacy policy (if any).

The Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) is a self-regulatory cooperative of online marketing and analytics companies. The NAI provides educational content and opt-out tools to help Internet users learn about and address online behavioral marketing practices. Through the NAI’s online options, you may opt out of particular NAI network members’ behavioral advertising programs or you may opt out of all NAI network members’ programs. Opting out will prevent the given network from which you opted out from using your Web preferences and usage patterns to deliver targeted online ads. The NAI opt-out only works with participating third party advertising networks that use cookies and Web beacons to execute their advertising initiatives. If you would like additional information about online behavioral marketing and your options regarding these standard Internet practices, please visit the NAI website at [http://www.networkadvertising.org/index.asp](https://www.networkadvertising.org/index.asp).

### Security Measures

Within ArkayBeverages.com, your information is kept on password protected, limited access servers. Wherever possible and applicable, ArKaybeverages.com servers reside behind a corporate firewall that maintains controls on access to the system from both our internal network and the Internet.

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA. Such staff maybe engaged in, the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Policy.

The transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. We will do our best to protect your personal data, but cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted and any transmission is at your own risk. Once your information is received, strict procedures and security features will be employed to endeavor to ensure unauthorized access. Also, as a security measure we “back up” the data stored on our systems, and such prior information cannot be completely removed from our databases. As a result, you should not expect that all of your personal information will be completely removed from our backed-up databases. It is your responsibility to protect the security of your login information. Please note that emails you send to us through our Website are not encrypted, and you should not communicate any confidential information through our Website.

### What Are Your Choices Regarding Collection, Use, And Distribution Of Your Information?

You may “opt-out,” or unsubscribe from our newsletters, emails or personalized on-line advertisements by following any unsubscribe instructions in any e-mail, newsletter or personalized on-line advertisement you receive from us, or sent on our behalf, or by sending an e-mail to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#cfbaa1bcbaadbcacbda6adaa8f8ebda4aeb68daab9aabdaea8aabce1aca0a2)

**Please Note:**  If you agree to receive e-mails from any of our third party service providers or any third party merchants on our site, you will receive e-mails separately from them, and information that you choose to disclose to them will be subject to the privacy policy of each. If you later decide that you no longer want to receive their e-mails, you will need to follow their own specific opt-out instructions.

### A Special Note About Children’s Privacy

You must be at least 18 years old to use this Website. Our policy is that we do not knowingly collect, use or disclose personally identifiable information about visitors under 18 years of age. If you are the parent or guardian of a child under 18 years of age and believe that they have disclosed personally identifiable information to us, please contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#2454564d5245475d6465564f455d6641524156454341570a474b49) so that we may delete the information.

### Privacy Policy Changes

This Policy was last changed on June 1, 2017. If ArKaybeverages.com makes changes to any terms or conditions of the Policy, the changes will be posted in this document so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and to whom we will disclose it. We may change, modify, add or remove portions of this Policy at any time, and any changes will become effective immediately upon being posted unless we tell you otherwise.

### Contacting Arkay About Privacy Questions Or Concerns

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact ArKaybeverages.com by sending a email to:

**Attn:**  Privacy Compliance Officer [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#1c6c6e756a7d7f655c5d6e777d655e796a796e7d7b796f327f7371)
